Hirsh Health Sciences Library Records UA225
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Slide library, 1893 -- 1998; UA225.004; 1.2 Linear Feet; 937 Digital Object(s)
  - Alumni, Accomplishments and Challenges, 1934 -- 1990; UA225.004.001.00006; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Wolfson, Louis, M '19, UA225.004.001.000006.00032; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Alumni and alumnae; Physicians; Slides (photographs); Wolfson, Louis E.; M1919
    - Tufts seal, UA225.004.001.000006.00033; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Seals; Slides (photographs); Tufts University
    - Tufts seal, UA225.004.001.000006.00034; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Tufts seal, UA225.004.001.000006.00035; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Tufts seal, UA225.004.001.000006.00036; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Deaning, UA225.004.001.000006.00037; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Deans (Education); Slides (photographs)
    - Deaning, UA225.004.001.000006.00038; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Problems of the Dean, UA225.004.001.000006.00039; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Changes at TUSM, 1934 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.000006.00040; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medical education--Statistics; Tuition; Enrollment, School; Slides (photographs)
    - Changes at TUSM, 1954 -- 1984; UA225.004.001.000006.00041; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Changes at TUSM, since, 1983-07-01; UA225.004.001.000006.00042; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Strengths of TUSM, UA225.004.001.000006.00043; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Excellence, UA225.004.001.000006.00044; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Summary - positives, UA225.004.001.000006.00045; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Problems, 1984; UA225.004.001.000006.00046; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Present problems, 1985; UA225.004.001.000006.00047; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Problems, UA225.004.001.000006.00048; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Summary: concerns, UA225.004.001.000006.00049; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Issues, UA225.004.001.000006.00050; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Previous problems, UA225.004.001.000006.00051; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Present problems, UA225.004.001.000006.00052; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Perilous Times, UA225.004.001.000006.00053; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Perilous Times, UA225.004.001.000006.00054; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Priorities, UA225.004.001.000006.00055; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Progress and Challenges, 1985 -- 1986; UA225.004.001.000006.00056; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Challenges, UA225.004.001.000006.00057; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Challenges, UA225.004.001.000006.00058; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Challenges, UA225.004.001.000006.00059; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Some suggestions, UA225.004.001.000006.00060; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Publications, UA225.004.001.000006.00061; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Conclusions from long range plan, UA225.004.001.000006.00062; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Conclusions from long range plan, UA225.004.001.000006.00063; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - National health expenditures, 1986; UA225.004.001.000006.00064; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Health Expenditures--statistics and numerical data--United States; Slides (photographs)
    - Federal government budget, 1986; UA225.004.001.000006.00065; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Health Expenditures--statistics and numerical data--United States; Budget; Slides (photographs)
    - Factors accounting for growth in medical care expenditures, 1973 -- 1984; UA225.004.001.000006.00066; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Veteran's benefits, US Budget in brief, 1987; UA225.004.001.000006.00067; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Veterans' benefits; Slides (photographs)
    - Medical care as percent of GNP, 1966 -- 1985; UA225.004.001.000006.00068; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Outlays for health, U.S. budget, 1987; UA225.004.001.000006.00069; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Medicare, U.S. budget in brief, 1987; UA225.004.001.000006.00070; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medicare--Finance--United States; Slides (photographs)
  - Students and professors at work, 1998; UA225.004.001.00007; Tufts University School of Medicine
    - Smiling man in purple x-ray coat, UA225.004.001.00007.00001; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Radiology; Faculty, Medical; Slides (photographs); Sarno, Robert C.
    - Five students with professor, UA225.004.001.00007.00002; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Problem-based learning; Medical education; Medical students; Slides (photographs)
    - John Richmond, UA225.004.001.00007.00003; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Orthopedics; Faculty, Medical; Slides (photographs); Richmond, John C.
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00004; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00005; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Mark Belsky, Ortho Surgery, UA225.004.001.00007.00006; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Orthopedics; Faculty, Medical; Slides (photographs); Sarno, Robert C.
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00007; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00008; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00009; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00010; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00011; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00012; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00013; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Radiology; Medical students; Faculty, Medical; Slides (photographs); Sarno, Robert C.
    - Students looking in microscopes, UA225.004.001.00007.00014; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medical students; Microscopes; Slides (photographs)
    - Students reading, UA225.004.001.00007.00015; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medical students; Medical literature; Slides (photographs)
    - Three students looking in microscopes, UA225.004.001.00007.00016; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00017; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00018; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00019; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00020; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00021; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00022; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00023; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00024; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00025; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00026; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in red x-ray coat, UA225.004.001.00007.00027; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00028; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Two doctors looking at x-ray, UA225.004.001.00007.00029; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Radiology; Medical students; Faculty, Medical; Slides (photographs); Lee, Mary Y.
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00030; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00031; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Man in purple and man in red x-ray coats, UA225.004.001.00007.00032; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students and professor at table in classroom, 1998-09; UA225.004.001.00007.00033; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Problem-based learning; Medical education; Medical students; Slides (photographs); Beresford, James
    - Two students and professor, UA225.004.001.00007.00034; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students and professor at table in classroom, UA225.004.001.00007.00035; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Three students reading, UA225.004.001.00007.00036; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students reading, UA225.004.001.00007.00037; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students and professor at table in classroom, UA225.004.001.00007.00038; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students looking in microscopes, UA225.004.001.00007.00039; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students looking in microscopes, 1998-09; UA225.004.001.00007.00040; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students and professor at blackboard, UA225.004.001.00007.00041; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medical students; Faculty, Medical; Nephrology; Slides (photographs); Harrington, John T.
    - Students and professor at blackboard, UA225.004.001.00007.00042; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students at table, UA225.004.001.00007.00043; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
      Medical students; African Americans; Problem-based learning; Slides (photographs)
    - Students looking in microscopes, UA225.004.001.00007.00044; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students reading, UA225.004.001.00007.00045; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
    - Students looking in microscopes, UA225.004.001.00007.00046; Tufts University (Box data_value_missing_1d1a7166b0b757fef417a2f7975e3623)
- Additional accessions, 1990 -- 2011; UA225.005; 92 Digital Object(s)
  - Electronic media to stabilize, 1990 -- 2010; UA225-014 (Box data_value_missing_dfcd90501592f341c2a5ee4375b03932, Box 1)
  - BLC Survey, 2000 -- 2001; UA225-015
  - Cora Ho's email, 2000 -- 2011; UA225-016
  - SlideWrite Plus Trial Size, 1988; UA225.065
  - WS 5, 1987--1994; UA225.066
  - Lib Budget 1990-91, 1990--1997; UA225.067
  - Lotus BR9091, 1989--1991; UA225.068
  - NA, 1990--1992; UA225.069
  - Vacation N-Y, 1994--1996; UA225.070
  - Vacation records M-Z, 1994; UA225.071
  - Vacation H-M, 1994--1996; UA225.072
  - ARL, 1994; UA225.073
  - Tulips Email, 1989--1995; UA225.074
  - Documentation, 1991--1995; UA225.075
  - ISPDQ, 1990--1993; UA225.076
  - SWP3, 1993--1994; UA225.077
  - Emails, 1993--1994; UA225.078
  - APDQo, 1990--1996; UA225.079
  - WP51 Graphics, 1990--1995; UA225.080
  - Copyright Procedures, 1994--1996; UA225.081
  - WP, 1989--1998; UA225.082
  - Policies Procedures, 1993--1998; UA225.083
  - Admin 2, 1986--1997; UA225.084
  - FACT93, 1993; UA225.085
  - ADL9192, 1980--1993; UA225.086
  - Graphic WP, 1992--1994; UA225.087
  - Back up, 1991--1993; UA225.088
  - Blank, 1986--1990; UA225.089
  - WP Cabinet Meetings, 1991--1996; UA225.090
  - ILL 90/91, 1990--1997; UA225.091
  - Lib resources hours, 1989--1997; UA225.092
  - AR_9091, 1991--1997; UA225.093
  - ADD0621, 1990--1993; UA225.094
  - 1992_93_worksheets, 1992--1995; UA225.095
  - WS_5, 1987--1994; UA225.096
  - Lib_Budget_1990_91, 1990--1997; UA225.097
  - Lotus BR9091, 1989--1991; UA225.098
  - PDQs, 1990--1995; UA225.099
  - LOTUS 1, 1985--1991; UA225.100
  - LOTUS 2 Back up, 1988; UA225.101
  - Fees 89, 1988--1990; UA225.102
  - Grateful Med Demo, 1986--1990; UA225.103
  - Blank, 2000; UA225.017; 2867.2 Megabytes; 16
  - Estes 9, 1998; UA225.018; 2764.8 Megabytes; 5
  - pbl, 1998; UA225.019; 0.28046875 Megabytes; 1
  - standalonedtd, 2000; UA225.020; 0.09736328125 Megabytes; 1
  - class meeting, 2001; UA225.021; 0.0388671875 Megabytes; 9
  - Bios, 1999--2002; UA225.022; 0.00126953125 Megabytes; 16
  - setuppi, 1998; UA225.023; 0.88154296875 Megabytes; 12
  - Performance, 2000; UA225.024; 0.85986328125 Megabytes; 8
  - File 2, 1997--1999; UA225.025; 1.3 Megabytes; 29
  - 32, 1997; UA225.026; 1.2 Megabytes; 3
  - 5 Back up 31, 1994--1999; UA225.027; 1.4 Megabytes; 36
  - 30, 1994--1999; UA225.028; 0.02421875 Megabytes; 36
  - 29, 1995--1999; UA225.029; 0.2416015625 Megabytes; 36
  - 28, 1996--2000; UA225.030; 0.82529296875 Megabytes; 59
  - 27, 1995--2000; UA225.031; 1.1 Megabytes; 39
  - Lotus 26, 1995--2000; UA225.032; 0.80791015625 Megabytes; 43
  - Lotus_25, 1995--2000; UA225.033; 1.4 Megabytes; 28
  - Lotus_24, 1994--2000; UA225.034; 1.2 Megabytes; 75
  - Recycle_1, 1995--2000; UA225.035; 1.4 Megabytes; 42
  - PDQs, 1997--1999; UA225.036; 1.1 Megabytes; 128
  - More_Files, 1998--1999; UA225.037; 1.4 Megabytes; 39
  - More_Files_3, 1995--1999; UA225.038; 1.3 Megabytes; 85
  - cH_Backups_Temp, 1996--2000; UA225.039; 1.3 Megabytes; 17
  - CH3_18, 1995--1999; UA225.040; 1.1 Megabytes; 40
  - ADMIN_Administration, 2001; UA225.041; 0.238671875 Megabytes; 15
  - Admin_99, 1999--2012; UA225.042; 0.60634765625 Megabytes; 6
  - Back_15, 1999--2002; UA225.043; 1.1 Megabytes; 4
  - NA, 1996--1999; UA225.044; 0.84375 Megabytes; 46
  - Recycle_2, 1994--2000; UA225.045; 0.05908203125 Megabytes; 55
  - ULC_Team, 2000--2012; UA225.046; 0.4294921875 Megabytes; 29
  - Policy_and_Procedures, 1998--2001; UA225.047; 1.3 Megabytes; 20
  - Excel 9, 1999; UA225.048; 0.99970703125 Megabytes; 11
  - MLANET 2000, UA225.049; 0.59658203125 Megabytes; 13
  - OPAL Mail, 1999--2000; UA225.050; 0.2365234375 Megabytes; 10
  - ULC Team, 2000--2001; UA225.051; 0.08623046875 Megabytes; 55
  - Orientation 01, 2001; UA225.052; 0.1751953125 Megabytes; 3
  - NER004, 2000; UA225.053; 1.4 Megabytes; 10
  - ADL9192, 1991--1993; UA225.054; 0.0400390625 Megabytes; 15
  - Graphic WP, 1992--1994; UA225.055; 0.30400390625 Megabytes; 5
  - Backup, 1991--1993; UA225.056; 0.47158203125 Megabytes; 26
  - CPI, 1985--1990; UA225.057; 0.3607421875 Megabytes; 14
  - FACT93, 1993; UA225.058; 0.6255859375 Megabytes; 4
  - Civic_Engagement_and_Internships_at_the_Democratic_Convention_July_2014, 2004; UA200.015.025.001; 0.50390625 Megabytes; 7
  - Five_Short_documentary-Films_produced_by_University_College_of_Citizenship_and_Public_Service_students_Spring_2004, UA200.015.025.002; 0.37021484375 Megabytes; 27
  - Cabinet Meeting, 1990--1996; UA225.059; 1.5 Megabytes; 89
  - In oxious, 1990--1998; UA225.060; 2.3 Megabytes; 136
  - Lib Resources Lib Hours, 1989--1997; UA225.061; 1.8 Megabytes; 77
  - AR Staot, 1991--1997; UA225.062; 2.3 Megabytes; 97
  - HHSL Disk1, 1990--1993; UA225.063; 0.546484375 Megabytes; 90
  - Worksheet2, 1992--1995; UA225.064; 2.3 Megabytes; 81